eblone.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy and Cookies | Eblone Wealth and Investment Management

Protecting your privacy is of vital importance to us. We have developed a privacy policy to help ensure your personal information remains private at all times. Below, we have answered the key questions about our privacy policy so that you can understand how we collect, use and protect your personal information. 

We will need to collect and process personal information from you to allow us to confirm your identity – for example, we may ask for your address, telephone number or bank account details when you open an account with us or if you apply for a product or for one of our investments. 

Your personal information will mainly be used by us to administer your account, although we may use your personal information for other operational reasons (for example, to carry out statistical analysis or for fraud prevention). If you give us permission we may also use your personal information for marketing purposes. 

We are committed to continually improving the service that we offer. To help provide training and guidance to our staff and to ensure we meet our legal and regulatory obligations, we may therefore also record and monitor electronic communications, including email and telephone calls. 

We may use your personal details to contact you, primarily by mail and email and also on occasion by telephone, so that we can provide you with information concerning products and services that may be of interest. 

If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us you can opt out at any time by phoning us on _+448433780176_ , writing to us at Dalton House, 60 Windsor Avenue, London, United Kingdom SW19 2RR,or by electronically unsubscribing from emails we have sent to you. 

We may, in some circumstances, ask other companies or organisations to provide information on our clients. This could involve the services of a credit reference agency or other third parties acting as our agents in order to help us identify a client.

__Financial advisers or any other party that you inform us about (if you no longer wish us to share your personal information with any such party, please let us know in writing).  
__Organisations that are part of our group of companies.  
__Regulators, governmental agencies, law enforcement agencies and any other person we reasonably think needs access to the data.  
__Any person to whom we have a right or duty to disclose personal data. For example, financial institutions may be required to provide certain transaction information to authorities or other official bodies to assist in the prevention of terrorism, money laundering and other crimes.  
__Marketing analysis purposes.  

All personal data that you provide to us will be treated with a high standard of security and confidentiality. Anti-fraud measures are used to protect your personal data (for example, bank details, passwords etc) used on our websites. We also encourage you to ensure that your computer is fully protected at all times when accessing your account.

Because we operate globally, personal data may be processed and disclosed in any country where we conduct business or have a service provider – including some countries that do not provide the same statutory level of data protection as the European Union’s Data Protection Directive. However in these circumstances we will strive to ensure the recipient agrees to keep your information confidential and that it is held securely in accordance with the requirements of the Data Protection Directive.

You can ask us, in writing, for a copy of the personal information that Eblone Wealth and Investment Management Limited holds on you. A fee may be chargeable for this information. If any personal data is found to be wrong, you have the right to ask us to amend or update the information that we hold. 

This site uses cookies to store information on your computer. This policy explains how we use cookies and may be amended, from time to time, without notice. By using this site you agree to the placement of cookies on your computer in accordance with the terms of this policy. If you do not wish to accept cookies from this site please either disable cookies or refrain from using this site. Please note that by disabling cookies in your browser settings this site may not function correctly.   

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can recognise you when you revisit and remember certain information about you. This can include which pages you have visited, choices you have made from menus, any specific information you have entered into forms and the time and date of your visit. 

This website uses three types of cookies:

__Strictly necessary cookies: These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided.  
__Performance cookies: These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.  
__Functionality cookies: These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.  

Please note that this website does not use targeting cookies or advertising cookies. To ensure that you are using this site with full and up-to-date information of how we use cookies please review this policy regularly as any amended policy will be updated on the site. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. However, you have the ability to disable cookies if you wish, generally through changing your internet software browsing settings. It may also be possible to configure your browser settings to enable acceptance of specific cookies or to notify you each time a new cookie is about to be stored on your computer enabling you to decide whether to accept or reject the cookie. To manage your use of cookies there are various resources available to you, for example the “Help” section on your browser may assist you. As our cookies allow you to access some of our website’s essential features we recommend that you leave cookies enabled, otherwise, if cookies are disabled, it may mean that you experience reduced functionality or will be prevented from using this site altogether.
